# **Bhavesh Shahani**

## JAVA BACKEND DEVELOPER

📞 +91 9575304562 😯 Bangalore,India. 🗵 gudd.shahani@gmail.com

in BhaveshShahani\_LinkedIn 🕠 BhaveshShahani\_Github

BhaveshShahani\_Twitter
BhaveshShahani\_Portfolio



#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMERY**

Software Developer with knowledge of technologies such as Java and JavaScript. Able to learn new technologies and software. Have an experience of 1000+ hours of Coding and Data Structure Algorithms. Team player who provides valuable support in a team environment.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Full Stack Web Developer**

*Masai School*Apr 2022 – present | Bangalore

#### 12th

Sanmati School May 2016 | Indore

#### 10th

CDS School 2014 | Nagpur

#### **CERTIFICATES**

• Diploma In Event Managment.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JAVA | JAVASCRIPT | HTML | CSS | DSA

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Team Work | Problem Solving | Motivated

## **INTERESTS**

Travelling | Hiking | Cooking

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Store Manager**

*Mithi Mirchi Cafe* 2019 – 2020 | Indore Worked as a Store Manager.

#### **Sales Manager**

*DAYA WorldWide PVT. LTD.*2017 – 2019 | Indore
Worked as a Sales Manager.

#### **PROJECTS**

### **Bewakoof Clone**

Bewakoof is a lifestyle fashion brand that makes creative, distinctive fashion for the trendy, contemporary Indian.

#### **Tech-Stack**

HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT

#### Responsibility

Product Page Design | Sorting

## **Bus Reservation Rest\_API**

Rest\_API using Spring Boot.

#### **Tech-Stack**

Java | SpringBoot | SQL | Hibernate | Swagger.

#### Responsibility

Feedback Section

\_\_\_\_\_

#### **Bath And Body Works Clone**

Bath & Body Work is an online eCommerce cosmetic brand, Which is a retail store chain that sells soaps, lotions, fragrances, and candles. .

#### **Tech-Stack**

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT

#### Responsibility

Team Lead | Layout of the website | Merging